Where are you today?
Sendai
Yes, sir.
Sendai, I mean.
It's morning.
I'm sure we'll have delicious food.
I can eat fresh pie.
So, let's have a good day.
Let's do our best for the day!
I'll do my best.
Thank you very much.
Let's go.
Yes, ma'am.
Hey, Yui.
Who are you eating in front with?
Musubikun.
Musubimaru.
With Musubimaru.
Ah!
Is it good?
I'm glad.
What did you think of it?
What about the food report?
I don't know.
The texture is...
Like it's melting.
Is it melting?
It's melting.
Really? That's good.
Just the right amount of salt.
I see.
It's good.
Well, I guess we're off to rehearsal.
Good luck with the rehearsal.
I'll do my best.
Bye-bye!
I've been told that I'll be the first one in the start rung to speak up.
I heard that you are the first one in the star troupe.
Oh, really?
It seems so
That's right.
Finally.
Let's get a move on.
Yes, sir.
And then...
You know what?
I'd like to be more vocal.
I hope I can make it more exciting.
I'll do my best.
Thank you very much.
Rehearsal is over.
So...
We have about 1 hour and 40 minutes
We have about an hour and 40 minutes.
We have a lot of time.
It's quite a bit.
It's only about 20 minutes.
I'm going to do your hair.
I'll do your face.
I do my makeup.
I do facial makeup.
I kill time.
I killed time.
I was killing time.
You know what?
I'll get you all set up in an hour and 40 minutes.
I'll see you in an hour and 40 minutes.
Go ahead. - How much time?
How long before the show?
Ten minutes.
Ten. Five minutes.
About six or seven minutes before the show, if I'm being precise.
That means you all know what time it is.
Oh, no.
Don't look.
So...
Today I'm almostToday I almost
Soro-chan did my makeup
Around the eyes
Result
I started to do it by myself, but
But after listening to Soro-chan
I was getting better and better.
What's that?
Huh?
I don't know...
I'm feeling a bit like Shiroyaki Hime today.
Too much!
Stop it!
I put a red ribbon on her ponytail.
Maybe that's why.
It's so cute.
And the weight of the bangs.
That's for sure.
The sides are really pretty, too.
It's snowing.
It's snowing on the side, too.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for doing my makeup.
Thank you.
Soro's back.
She won't tell me where she went.
Cute place.
Let's go there!
I'll go.
What are you talking about?
We're going now, really? - Yeah.
Yeah, 15 minutes ago.
And talk shit about Momochan.
Yeah.
I'm looking forward to it.
Why don't you laugh, Moo-chan?
Bye bye.
Bye bye!
You're the best!
You're the best
Great.
Great job.
Great job!
Goo-chan
Yay!
Yes, ma'am.
Bye bye
Andies
Let's see how they come.
One minute.
All right.
That's two quarters of the way through.
Yes, sir.
Today... is my first time.
Thank you.
I'll do my best.
Careful, careful, careful.
Let's be polite.
Yes, ma'am.
Mei mei mei.
Hey, guys.
Everybody.
OK.
Last one.
Good luck, everybody.
Please.
~~
Congratulations.
~~~~
~~
Congratulations.
This is Dora.
Thank you.
The show's over.
And after that...
After the show.
Congratulations.
I'm off.
Bye bye.
I'm waiting for the award show...
Kanere
I'm going to eat the kanerae that Ruri's father gave me
Bon appétit!
I'm eating it.
The second one
The second one.
We're the first ones, right?
The first one.
Bon appétit.
This is impossible.
I don't know.
Oh, my God.
Bon appétit!
It's so crispy!
So crispy!
Ri, you finished it.
I finished it.
I ate it on my own earlier.
Delicious.
Kanere is hard, right?
Come to think of it...
But aren't they totally different from mono-yan?
Some are squishy around the edges
I like rice cakes with a crunchy outside and a soft inside.
I like mochi.
You like it?
Here you go.
I wonder if it's locked.
But it's on the side, so it might be closed.
It's delicious.
Thanks for coming.
Are you the kind of guy who eats?
I'm eating a lot.
You're eating too much.
Seven cups?
I think it's seven refrigerators.
I want some too.
Bon appétit.
Ouch. Ouch.
Delicious.
It tastes like coffee.
And I can eat Ammar.
I can eat Ammar's coffee, too.
It's so raggedy
It looks so good on you!
This is from Tokyo.
Is there a Bogue?
What kind of store?
BOB.
It's on the Keiyo Line.
Keiyo Line?
Keiyo Line.
The one that goes to Maehama.
The tall one.
The one on top.
Tokyo's hail
Leaves.
Kyoyo Line?
Does the Keiyo Line exist?
Thank you very much.
Kyoyo?
Not Keiyo.
Keiyo?
Kyoyo.
Kyoyo.Kyoyo
Like Maehama?
Yes, sir.
Kyoyo.
Keiyo.
Keiyo Line.
Everyone, please buy at Keiyo.
I like raspberry in this one.
This is the second one, right?
Same flavor. Second one.
This is the first one.
The first one.
I'm having a fresh pie right now.
It's delicious.
Sweet.
Cookie dough.
Fresh cream.
Cream.
Combined.
It's so delicious!
What is it?
Shaped like a tart
Yes, yes, yes.
It's like a cream puff.
It spills over
Over there
That's all
It's snack time!
It's snack time.
Bye-bye.
There are four of us here now.
Here's another one.
Ruri is here.
And Sora is here, too.
It was fun, wasn't it?
It was fun.
It reminded me of you.
Yes, it was.
I don't know.
Cosmic Flotilla.
I think it was the most exciting time ever.
It was amazing, wasn't it?
I look forward to working with you in the future.
Let's have fun!
Only 4 more days to go!
We only have 4 shows left.
Next stop...
Fukuoka.
Fukuoka!
I'm looking forward to Fukuoka.
I'm looking forward to it again.
I'll see you later.
But...
There are six shows.
There are only six shows, so...
I hope you'll all come.
Please come to as many
Please come where you can.
I look forward to seeing you there.
I'm looking forward to seeing you at the other shows.
Let's do our best!
That's all for now.
That's all.
This is Unka.
Bye bye.
Thank you very much.
Bye-bye.
I'm going home.
That was fun.
How was it?
It was fun.
I'm full.
That makes two of us.
The two of you looking ahead...
Ayumi and...
Mr. Yuki is here.
Let's go home.
See you later.See you later.
Until the next
Until the Fukuoka show
Please wait for us.
Later, Momochan!
I want you to film the ending on stage.
Okay.
bye-bye!
progressed
Odai Odai
E?
Big wave
I can't.
No?
I'm not coming.
Mime
Sub-sub
O JA
O
Haya
MIME